Mr. Moksadul Hassan



Contact

Address:

House#14, Road#31, Block#D, Mirpur#12, Dhaka#1216

Phone:

+88 (0)1521200326

Email:

mdmoksadulhassanjibon@gmail.com

Languages

English – Excellent Bangla – Excellent Hindi- Average

Summary

Professional Experienced at Finance & Accounting Terms. Executive at Ad Operations/Ad Trafficking/Campaigning. Excellent Knowledge In SEO/Affiliate/CPA/Online/Digital Marketing. Strong Using ability in Google Ad Manager/Ad Trafficking Platform. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Finance & Accounting
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

- 1) Executive (Digital Ad Operations/QA)- 10/2019 to Present Service Engine Ltd, Mohakhali, Dhaka-1205, Bangladesh.
 - Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
 - Ad Operations/Ad Trafficking/Campaigning/Reporting.
 - SEO/Affiliate/CPA/Online/Digital Marketing.
- 2) Intern (Micro Credit Functions)- 7/2019 to 9/2019 Grameen Bank, Head Office, Mirpur#2, Dhaka#1216, Bangladesh
 - Performed Micro Credit financing and loan disbursement.
- 3) Trainee (SEO/ Digital Marketing)- 10/2018-01/2019 BASIS-BITM, 3rd Floor, BDBL Bhaban, East 12, Dhaka 1215.

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration: **BBA (Hon's) Professional,** Finance & Accounting- 2018

National University, Bangladesh

Certifications

- 1. Basic Finance & Accounting
- 2. MS Word/PPT/Excel/Hardware/Software Maintenance
- 3. Basic Google Ad Manager/DFP
- 4. SEO/Affiliate/CPA/Online/Digital Marketing.